<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<modDesc descVersion="106">
        <title>Roleplay Invoices</title>
        <description>
                    Created by MarlboroRedMan and Claude (Anthropic)

                    A multiplayer-ready invoicing and communication system for Farming Simulator 25 roleplay servers. Send invoices between farms, track payments, and ping other players - all from your in-game phone.

                    GETTING STARTED
                    Press F7 to open and close the phone from anywhere in the game.

                    INVOICES
                    Navigate to the Invoices app to access your Inbox and Outbox. To create a new invoice, tap + Create Invoice, select the recipient farm, choose a category, enter the amount and any details, then hit Send Invoice.

                    Recipients can Pay Invoice to transfer funds directly between farms, or Reject it if disputed. The sender can use Mark as Paid to manually close an invoice paid outside the system.

                    IMPORTANT: Always save your game after paying an invoice to ensure the money transfer persists. Unsaved sessions may revert the balance but the invoice status will remain PAID.

                    PINGS
                    Use the Ping app to send a quick message to any farm. Choose from preset messages or select Custom Message and type your own. The recipient gets an in-game notification instantly.

                    TEXT INPUT
                    Text fields do not support backspace or delete. Use the red X button at the end of each field to clear it and retype.

                    MANAGING INVOICES
                    To archive or delete invoices, stop the server, open roleplayInvoices.xml in your savegame folder, remove the invoice lines you want gone, save the file, then restart. Do not edit this file while the server is running.

                    MULTIPLAYER
                    All invoices and farm data sync automatically when a player connects. Invoices sent to offline farms will be waiting in their inbox when they join.
        </description>

        <version>0.1.0</version>
        <author>MarlboroRedMan and Claude (Anthropic)</author>
        <iconFilename>textures/icon.dds</iconFilename>
        <multiplayer supported="true"/>

        <extraSourceFiles>
                    <sourceFile filename="scripts/Invoice.lua"/>
                    <sourceFile filename="scripts/InvoiceManager.lua"/>
                    <sourceFile filename="scripts/InvoiceSave.lua"/>
                    <sourceFile filename="scripts/InvoiceEvents.lua"/>
                    <sourceFile filename="scripts/ContactManager.lua"/>
                    <sourceFile filename="scripts/RoleplayPhone.lua"/>
        </extraSourceFiles>

        <l10n filenamePrefix="localization/l10n"/>
</modDesc>
